{"results":

    [{"question":"What country did the plane crash in Indiana Jones and The Temple of Doom", "correct_answer":"India","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},
    {"question":"What is Frasier's last name in the TV show Frasier?", "correct_answer":"Crane","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},
    {"question":"What is the the enchanter's name in Monty Python and the Holy Grail?", "correct_answer":"Tim","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},
    {"question":"In a plotline of theTV show Seinfield, what is the name of the pilot written for NBC?", "correct_answer":"Jerry","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},
    {"question":"What is printed on Chef's apron in the TV show Southpark?", "correct_answer":"Chef","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},
    {"question":"In the movie Star Wars: A New Hope, what was the name of the planet destroyed by the Death Star?", "correct_answer":"Alderaan","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},
    {"question":"In the TV show The Simpsons, who is Patty and Selma's favourite celebrity?", "correct_answer":"MacGyver","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},
    {"question":"What Australian animal cannot walk backwards?", "correct_answer":"Emu","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},
    {"question":"What is the name of the river that runs through Paris?", "correct_answer":"Seine","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},
    {"question":"Which brand of beer features a kangaroo on the packaging?", "correct_answer":"Fosters","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},
    {"question":"What was the first widely used synthetic fiber?", "correct_answer":"Rayon","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},
    {"question":"What is the name of Goku's father in Dragonball Z?", "correct_answer":"Bardock","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},
    {"question":"In 1992, what country saw the opening of Euro Disneyland?", "correct_answer":"France","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},
    {"question":"At which castle can the Blarney Stone be found?", "correct_answer":"Blarney","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},
    {"question":"In North western Africa, this country is home to major cities Casablanca & Marrakech?", "correct_answer":"Morocco","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},
    {"question":"What is the acronym for 'random access memory'?", "correct_answer":"RAM","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},
    {"question":"In the comic Peanuts, this character always pulls the football away from Charlie Brown?", "correct_answer":"Lucy","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},
    {"question":"What is calcium oxide commonly called?", "correct_answer":"Lime","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},
    {"question":"Charles Lindbergh famouly took only four of these to eat with him on his transatlantic flight?", "correct_answer":"Sandwich","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},
    {"question":"A 'bunya-bunya' tree is native to which country?", "correct_answer":"Australia","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},
    {"question":"With age, what organ shrinks faster in males than in females?", "correct_answer":"Brain","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},
    {"question":"What is an organism called that lives on or in a host animal?", "correct_answer":"Parasite","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},
    {"question":"Before Canberra, which city was the capital of Australia?", "correct_answer":"Melbourne","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},
    {"question":"Austin is the capital of what US state?", "correct_answer":"Texas","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},
    {"question":"What constellation is represented by scales in Astrology?", "correct_answer":"Libra","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},
    {"question":"What is the Zodiac sign of the water carrier?", "correct_answer":"Aquarius","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},
    {"question":"Boston, Massachusetts is also known as?", "correct_answer":"Beantown","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},
    {"question":"What Dutch master painted 64 self-portraits?", "correct_answer":"Rembrandt","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},
    {"question":"Arachnoid refers to what kind of insect?", "correct_answer":"Spider","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]},
    {"question":"Are most cats right pawed or left pawed?", "correct_answer":"Left","incorrect_answers":["a","b","c"]}]}